Previously, on AMC's "The Walking Dead".
《行尸走肉》前情提要
Get up. We're breaking you out.
起来  我们救你出去
I'm not going with you.
我不跟你们走
It's not your time.
你命不该绝
Somebody opened the door for him.
有人为他开门了
We decided to protect ourselves no matter what.
我们决定不管怎么样  都要保护好自己
We would stay hidden, and we would stay alive.
我们会一直躲在这里  一直活下去
Tara, you've been out further than any of us.
塔拉  你在外面比我们走得都远
At least you can tell us where not to look.
至少你能告诉我们别去哪找
Yeah, sure thing.
当然可以
They -- They have guns.
她们有枪
A lot of them.
许多枪
I saw it.
我看见了
What?
什么
That group.
那个团体
Um, the women I met.
我遇见的女人们
They have an armory. They have guns.
她们有武器库  有枪
Why didn't you tell us before now?
你之前怎么不跟我们说
I made a promise, Rick.
我做过保证  瑞克
Do you ever think about who you've killed?
你会想起你杀掉的人吗
Yeah.
会
Are you ready if this goes south?
如果计划失败  你有心理准备吗
It won't.
不会失败的
If it does, you don't need to feel bad.
如果失败了  你不必内疚
I do feel bad.
我的确内疚
I will.
我会内疚的
Tara...
塔拉
you don't have to.
你不必
You need ?to cover this with a tarp.
你得用一块防水布盖住
- A tarp? ?- Tarp.
-防水布吗  -对
Why?
为什么
Think about it.
你想想
Okay. Just tell me.
直接告诉我吧
We want warmth
我们需要保温
so they'll put out shoots before the last freeze.
这样它们就会在冬天来临之前发芽
That way, we pull back the tarp,
那样的话  我们扯掉防水布
they die naturally,
它们就会自然枯亡
saves on all the endless weeding.
就不用一直除草了
Get to tarping.
去盖防水布吧
You got it, boss lady.
没问题  女老大
Uh, wait. Where are you going?
等等  你去哪
I, uh -- I'm not a farmer.
我不是农民
I need some help here.
我需要帮助
No, you don't.
你不需要
I saw a wild blueberry bush growing outside.
我看见外面长着野生蓝莓灌木丛
If it's young enough,
如果足够嫩
I'm gonna pull it up and replant it here.
我就要把它拔出来  种在这里
Good one will produce for over 40 years.
好植株能结40多年的蓝莓
We got to start acting like we'll be around that long.
我们得开始规划活那么久了
Cool. Yeah.
挺好的
Just tarp. Don't touch.
就盖防水布  别碰
I'll see how you do after.
之后我来看看你做得怎么样
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
原创翻译  双语字幕
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
最新连载海外影视剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com 仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Once you're up, watch for the signal.
你上去后  注意信号
What time does the clock start?
几点开始
Soon as she's in.
等她一进去就开始
You good?
你没事吧
I'm good enough.
后期     送小哥  拉图
I'm glad you came. I know it's been hard.
很高兴你来了  我知道这很难
- I know you don't want this. - Didn't want this,
-我知道你不想这样  -我之前不想
but I'm starting to understand what's on the menu now.
但我现在开始明白是怎么回事了
We can hide like these people,
我们可以像这些人一样躲藏
we can keep trying to serve The Saviors,
我们可以继续供奉救世军
and I can watch you get randomly beaten every so often,
我可以时常看见你被毒打
or else we can fight.
或者我们可以反抗
So, here we are.
所以我们来了
And being with you, well...
而且跟你在一起
it makes abject terror tolerable.
让无助的恐惧可以容忍了
I should've tried harder to stop Rosita and Sasha.
我该更努力地阻止罗西塔和萨沙的
If they'd have just waited one more day...
如果她们再等一天...
Well, Sasha's a good shot,
萨沙枪法很好
and Rosita knows how to take care of herself.
罗西塔知道如何照顾自己
Probably back at Hilltop right now.
她们也许现在都回山顶寨了
Least I hope so. We're gonna need 'em.
至少我希望如此  我们需要她们
There's a whole lot of people still got to die.
还得死很多人的
Hey, there.
你好啊
You okay?
没事吧
Can I get some water?
能给我点水吗
I should introduce myself.
我该自我介绍一下
I'm David.
我是大卫
I wonder if you remember me from last night.
不知道你昨晚是否记得我
Do you?
你记得吗
No.
不记得
Well, I can forgive that.
我能原谅你
Last night was kind of a shitstorm.
昨晚简直一团乱
I was the guy that gave the rope to the guys that tied you up.
就是我把绳子递给那些人  把你绑起来的
I always keep some close.
我总是带着一些绳子
There's just all kinds of fun and interesting things you can do with rope.
用绳子能做许多有趣的事情
God, you're pretty.
天啊  你真漂亮
If I give you some water,
如果我给你水喝
which is not something I'm supposed to do,
这是我不该做的事
will you do something for me?
你愿意为我做点事吗
Something you're not supposed to do?
做点你不该做的事
Will you?
你愿意吗
Tell me how thirsty you are.
告诉我你有多渴
Go to hell.
去死吧
Oh, shit.
该死
Fighting's just gonna make it last longer.
反抗只会让过程更持久
Which, for the record, is fine by me.
告诉你  我无所谓
?David!
大卫
What the hell are you doing in here?
你他妈在这里干什么呢
Negan, sir --
尼根  先生
Do you really think I need you to answer that?
你真觉得我需要你回答吗
I can see that you're trying to rape this woman.
我能看出你想强奸这女人
You were trying to rape this woman, weren't you?
你想强奸这女人  对吧
This is some unacceptable behavior.
这是不可接受的行为
Rape is against the rules here.
强奸违反了这里的规定
I wouldn't wanna be somewhere where it wasn't.
我可不想待在允许强奸的地方
Someone in charge who let something like that fly...
负责的人放过这种事...
David.
大卫
You really crossed a line here.
你真的越线了
I'm sorry, sir.
抱歉  先生
You know what?
知道吗
I do not accept your apology.
我不接受你的道歉
Get, uh...
给...
Sasha.
萨沙
That is a beautiful name.
名字真好听
Get Sasha here a new T-shirt.
给萨沙拿件新衬衫
I'm sorry you had to see that.
很抱歉让你看到了这些
Sorry 'bout the rope, too.
绳子的事我也很抱歉
Probably overkill,
也许有些小题大做
but you did cause one hell of a fracas last night.
但你昨晚闹了好大一场事
Oh, shit.
该死
I remember you.
我记得你
Yeah.
嗯
You were there.
你当时在场
Oh, hell. I get it now.
该死  我现在懂了
I got to hand it to you.
我得承认
You've got some beach-ball-sized lady nuts on you,
你这娘们真他妈有种
coming in all kamikaze like that.
不顾死活地就冲进来了
Big question here,
问题是
and I need the truth on this one --
我需要你说实话
Did Rick put you up to this?
是瑞克派你来的吗
Rick?
瑞克
Your bitch?
你的狗吗
No.
不是
Either way, you must've thought it was gonna be the end,
不管怎样  你肯定以为你必死无疑
coming in on your lonesome like that.
毕竟你那样独自闯进来
But that's not the way it's got to go.
但事情不会这样发展
Unh-unh. Just the opposite.
恰恰相反
See, this...
这
Well, this could be the beginning.
这可能只是个开始
This knife is yours now.
刀现在归你了
You can try to use it, take me out,
你可以试着使用  干掉我
but considering I am standing above you,
但考虑到我站在你上方
holding a baseball bat,
拿着一根球棒
that doesn't seem real smart.
那可不是明智之举
Now, you can use it to slit your wrists,
你可以用刀来割腕
which would be a damn shame, but I get it.
这就太可惜了  但我懂
You're obviously not on the shiny side of the street,
考虑到最近发生的事  你显然
given recent events.
不是什么阳光女人
Now, you can sit there and do nothin',
你可以坐在那里  什么也不做
wait for ol' David to come back to life and eat your face,
等着老大卫复活  咬掉你的脸
also a damn shame and kinda nuts,
这也很可惜  有些疯狂
but, hell, to each their own.
但你有权做出选择
Or you can use that blade and stop ol' Rapey David
或者你可以用刀来干掉强奸犯老大卫
from becoming Dead-Alive Rapey David,
阻止他变成强奸犯行尸大卫
save yourself, join the cause.
自己救自己  加入救世军
I know what I'd do.
我知道我要拿你怎么办
What?
怎么办
I'm a man short.
我少了个男丁
Hell, you can't really call this piece of shit a man,
妈的  这个人渣算不上男人
but still, I'm short,
但依然  我少了人
and you got those beach-ball-sized lady nuts,
而你这娘们有种极了
and I wanna harness the heat comin' off of 'em.
我想要好好利用你的勇气
You can help me run this place one day,
有朝一日你可以帮我管理这个地方
all of us together, following the rules,
我们所有人一起  跟着规矩走
workin' on the same side of things.
站在同一战线
That's all this was ever about.
从来都是这么回事
And it still can be for you.
你依然可以选这条路
I know it's hard to picture,
考虑到我的所作所为
considering what I did.
我知道这有点难以想象
But, Sasha, we all got shit to get over.
但是  萨沙  人人都有必须迈过去的坎
Take some time. Think about it.
花点时间  好好想想
Whatever you decide, so it shall be.
无论你的决定如何  都由你说了算
No pressure.
别有压力
And, again, I am sorry you had to see that,
还有  再次道歉  很抱歉你不得不目睹那幕
even though I know you have seen some things.
虽然我知道你是见过场面的
I just want you to understand...
我只希望你能明白...
we are not monsters.
我们不是怪物
What did they do to you?
他们把你怎么了
They're keepin' me safe.
他们在保护我
I brought you some creature comforts.
我给你带了些能让你舒服点的东西
Full disclosure, the pillow is not hypoallergenic.
实话说  这枕头不防过敏
There was some debate as to whether or not I should come in here.
关于我该不该过来有过一些争论
They said in the event of a hostage situation with the pig sticker
他们说假如我被你携刀劫持的话
that I would fully be on my own.
我就只能靠自己了
Just wanted to share that.
我就这么一说
Negan relayed to me his offer to you.
尼根向我传达了他对你的招安之意
It's my opinion that you should accept said offer,
在我看来你应该接受
just as I did.
就像我一样
I know it's a hold-your-nose situation,
我知道这是不得已而为之
but taking up with the management here
但与这里的头头做朋友
was indeed the correct select.
真的是正确的选择
You know, I believed I could be brave,
我曾经认为自己可以勇敢起来
that I could be a survivor like Abraham was,and ...
当一个亚伯拉罕那样的生存者...
ridin' that RV into the sunset was...
开着那辆房车驶向夕阳是...
some of the greatest 37 minutes of my existence.
我一生中最棒的37分钟
But I know now that I was full-tilt delusional.
但我如今明白那只是一个完全不切实际的幻想
I have never in my life been as scared
我这辈子最害怕的一次
as I was that night in the woods,
就是那晚在那个林子里
kit to the grit,
跪在地上
fully believing my number's about to be called,
觉得自己死定了
then seeing it happen to someone brave...
然后看见勇敢的生存者...
to a survivor.
被杀了
And then the pants-pissing terror
然后那种让人吓尿裤子的恐惧
of the rinse and repeat of that very same event --
看着那个场景一次又一次重现...
I just...
我...
I couldn't.
我做不到
Being here means I'll never have to again.
来这边意味着我再不用恐惧了
And neither will you if you just say "yes."
假如你答应的话  你也不用了
Please say "yes."
求求你答应吧
He would want you to.
他希望你能答应
He wouldn't.
他不希望
I do.
我希望
We're still here.
我们依然活着
Things have changed.
世道已经变了
We can change with 'em. We have to.
我们可以随之做出改变  我们必须如此
Go.
走吧
- He's, uh, starting to... - Please.
-他已经开始...  -拜托了
Don't think I've seen you outside the walls.
我还从没见过你到墙外来呢
Well, I built these walls to use them.
我建这些围墙就是为了用的
If I want greenery, I eat a salad.
假如我想吃绿菜了  我可以吃沙拉
Then why are you here?
那你为什么来这里
I was hoping we could talk.
我本打算找你谈谈
Then I saw you come out here alone.
然后我看见你一个人跑出来
I was concerned.
我很担心你
Where are your friends?
你的朋友们呢
They went out.
他们出去了
They're looking for something they need.
他们在找需要的东西
Without you?
你不去吗
Now, I'm just wondering -- Why you still here, Maggie?
我只是好奇  你怎么还留在这  玛姬
With Carson gone...
卡森已经不在了
I heard you were gonna get him back.
我听说你要救他回来
That not true?
不是吗
Was it just something you said?
还是只是说说而已
Maggie, you've got to start trusting me.
玛姬  你得信任我
You know, people are tense, they're worried.
人们都很紧张  很担心
Everybody'd be a hell of a lot better
如果我们表现得像一伙
if we could present a-a united front.
大家会安心得多
It would be a lot easier if we actually were a united front.
如果我们能真正成为一伙  会轻松得多
You're right.
你说得对
I need to be more open to working together.
我得对合作持更开放的态度
I apologize.
我道歉
I never intended for things between us to come to this point.
我从不希望我们之间闹成这样
I appreciate that.
感谢你这么说
It's never too late to change. You know that?
亡羊补牢永远不晚  知道吗
If you're serious, I'll come by later and we can talk more.
如果你是认真的  我稍后会找你详谈
Fine.
好
Great.
太好了
I thought this'd just take a second.
我还以为很快就能完事
Would you mind keeping an eye out while I finish up?
弄完之前  你能帮我留意一下四周吗
Could you do that?
可以吗
Happy to.
乐意之至
We got one.
来了一只
I'll do it.
我来
I'm here to protect the pregnant lady.
我是来保护孕妇的
Don't need the pregnant lady to protect me.
不用孕妇保护我
Have you ever killed one before?
你以前杀过行尸吗
I wouldn't be here if I hadn't.
没杀过我就不可能站在这了
- It's fine. I got it. - No.
-没事  我来吧  -不
Jesus.
天啊
Fine. Do it.
好吧  你来
Maggie!
玛姬
Please help me!
救救我
You okay?
你没事吧
He hasn't killed one before.
他以前没杀过行尸
He's learning.
正在学习
That's not what he told us.
他跟我们可不是这么说的
Thanks for the help.
谢谢你救我
You catch that yourself?
你自己抓到的吗
- Shit, yeah. - ?Rachel.
-那他妈当然  -?瑞秋
I mean, yeah.
我是说  那当然
- Gonna go clean it. - Okay.
-我去把它清理干净  -好
Stay quiet
别出声
and put your hands on your head.
手放头上
We should've just killed you in the village.
在村里时我们就该杀了你
You're gonna be glad you didn't.
你会庆幸你们没杀我的
You're not alone, are you?
你不是一个人来的  对吧
Sit.
坐下
What do you want?
你想干什么
I want you to sit.
我想让你坐下
Hey, Cyndie.
你好  辛蒂
You promised.
你保证过的
Yeah. I did.
对  我保证过
Put your hands on your head.
把手放在头上
I didn't have a choice.
我别无选择
Why are you here?
你来这干什么
I said I didn't have a choice.
我说了  我别无选择
But you do, both of you do.
但你们有  你俩都有
My friends are out there right now,
我的同伴现在就在外面
and they're gonna take this place, hopefully without firing a shot.
他们会攻占这里  希望不必开火
What? You're...you're gonna "Take this place"?
什么  你们要"攻占这里"
What are you talking about?
你在说什么
We need your guns.
我们需要你们的枪
What?
什么
We're gonna fight The Saviors.
我们要抵抗救世军
- You should join us. ?- No.
-你们应该加入我们  -不
The Saviors killed your fathers,
救世军杀害了你们的父亲
your brothers, husbands, sons, and you ran from them.
兄弟  丈夫  儿子  而你们选择逃避
I thought we got rid of them.
我以为我们铲除了他们
Beatrice said there was more out there, and she was right.
碧翠丝说还有更多救世军  她说得对
They came back.
他们回来了
They killed my friends.
杀了我的朋友们
They killed my girlfriend.
杀了我的女友
They took us over. They took everything from us.
接管了我们  夺走了我们的一切
We do whatever The Saviors tell us to do,
我们对救世军千依百顺
and they think we're still doing that, but we're not.
他们以为我们依然效忠  但不是
We're gonna fight them.
我们打算反抗
And we have other communities beside us,
还有其他社区加入我们
and with Oceanside, we would have an army.
有了海边旅馆  我们就有了一支军队
So, that's it?
就这样吗
"Thanks for the guns. You should join us"?
"谢谢给枪  你们应该加入我们"
If we fight them together, we can beat them.
如果我们联手  可以打败他们
We have to try.
我们必须试试
They'll win, Tara. I've seen it. So have you.
他们会赢的  塔拉  我见过  你也见过
Just talk to the leader of my group, Rick.
和我们团队的首领谈谈  瑞克
Just talk, and we don't have to take over this place.
只用谈谈  我们不必攻占这里
We don't want to.
我们不想那样做
I can give them the signal to stop this,
我可以示意他们停下
but you have to tell me right now.
但是你必须现在就告诉我
Listen. We're not just hiding in the woods.
听着  我们不只是藏在树林里
We're doing something. We're not giving up.
我们在做事  我们没有放弃
I didn't want to break my promise, Cyndie, okay?
我不想打破我的承诺  辛蒂
But the world can belong to good people, to fair people,
但是世界可以属于好人  公正的人
if we're all just brave enough to try.
只要我们有足够的勇气去尝试
We are not good, and we are not brave.
我们不是好人  也不勇敢
Neither you nor me.
你我都不是
She is.
她是
That's why we're in this mess.
所以我们才有现在这麻烦
Look, Tara, if you take our guns,
塔拉  如果你们拿走我们的枪
you might as well be killing us all.
还不如把我们全杀了
That's what you'll be doing.
这就是你们做的事
We should talk to them.
我们应该和他们谈谈
No.
不
We can try to stop this.
我们可以试着阻止这事
No, Cyndie.
不  辛蒂
It doesn't matter.
无所谓了
You can't.
没法阻止了
Go! Go!
走
The arsenal!
武器库
On the ground. Now.
趴下  快
Those hands -- Put them on your head.
手抱头
Please.
拜托
Your people killing my people?
你的人杀我的人
The bombs were outside the walls.
炸弹安置在墙外
You could've stopped this.
你本可以阻止的
Look, I hope everyone is okay. I do.
我希望所有人都没事  真的
They better be.
最好没事
Stand up.
起来
It's time to move.
该走了
It's my legs.
我的腿
Stop, stop. Back up. Back up.
站住  后退
Cyndie, stop!
辛蒂  别动
It's empty. ?What?
是空的  什么
It's unloaded.
没装弹
We didn't come here to hurt anybody.
我们不是来伤人的
Cyndie, give it here.
辛蒂  给我
Now.
快
Natania, just talk to Rick.
娜塔尼亚  就和瑞克谈谈
Shut up.
闭嘴
Everybody down!
所有人蹲下
Hands on your heads.
手放头上
Everybody stay calm.
所有人冷静
We don't want anyone to get hurt.
我们不想伤害任何人
Stay down and listen to what we say.
别动  听我们说
We want this to go as simply and as peacefully as possible.
我们想让这件事尽量简单和平地解决
All of you can make it that way.
你们都可以做到
Get down over there. Keep quiet.
去那边蹲着  安静
Now, we made a lot of noise.
我们搞出了很大动静
We want to wrap this up quick so you can send people
所以我们想尽快了事  这样你们就可以派人
to redirect anything coming this way.
引开过来的行尸
Tara said your forests are relatively clear,
塔拉说你们这片森林比较稀疏
so we won't take any chances.
所以我们不会冒险
No one needs to get hurt.
任何人都不必受伤
This is just about what you have, what we need.
重要的只是你们有什么  我们需要什么
Nobody's taking anything.
没人可以带走任何东西
You need to let everyone go
放了所有人
and leave right now.
立刻离开
Just walk away or this one dies.
离开  不然她就得死
Yeah, we'll leave you alone.
好  我们会离开
But we're taking your weapons with us.
但我们要带走你们的武器
That's not gonna change.
这点不会改变
It's Natania, right?
你是娜塔尼亚  对吗
Put the gun down,
放下枪
and let's talk about what we can change.
我们来谈谈我们可以改变什么
No. Leave right now.
不  马上离开
Michonne, don't!
米恩琼  不要
We just wanna be left alone.
我们只是不想被打扰
Yeah, we'll leave you alone.
没问题  我们会离开
Just let go of her. Now.
立刻放开她
Or we'll kill you.
不然我们就杀了你
None of us want that.
我们都不想那样
They want us to fight The Saviors.
他们想让我们反抗救世军
We tried that. We lost. Too much.
我们试过  输了  输得很惨
We're not gonna lose anymore --
我们不会再失去任何东西了
not our guns, not our safety,
不管是我们的枪  还是我们的安全
not after everything we've done to get here.
我们做了那么多  好不容易才来这里
We're gonna win --
我们会赢的
with your guns, with or without your help.
只要有了你们的枪  无论你们帮不帮我们
Natania, put the gun down.
娜塔尼亚  放下枪
You kill me, and you die.
杀了我你也会死
And my people take the guns and nothing changes.
我们的人一样会拿走枪  什么都不会变
Maybe we should try.
也许我们应该试一下
Grandma, stop.
祖母  住手吧
It's over.
结束了
Just talk to them, okay?
和他们谈谈吧  好吗
It's not over!
还没完
They've forgotten.
他们都忘了
You've all forgotten.
你们都忘了
Some of you actually want to fight them?
你们中有些人真想反抗他们吗
After everything?
经历了那一切以后
We can lose our guns,
我们可以失去枪
but us leaving this place to fight?
但我们也要离开这里去战斗吗
After everything?
经历了那么多事以后
I have to remind you!
我必须提醒你们
Yes.
是的
I am gonna do this, and then I'm gonna die.
我会这样做  我会死
But it's that important.
但就是这么重要
This is your life, all of you.
这是你们的人生  你们所有人的
Remember what it looks like.
想想它是什么样的
Remember what they did to us!
想想他们以前是怎么对我们的
You need to see this. Open your eyes!
你们要看清楚  睁眼好好看着
Rick! Walkers!
瑞克  有行尸
Everybody up!
所有人起来
Get the children behind us!
让孩子们站到后面
They're coming.
它们过来了
First shift, join them on the line.
第一班  跟他们站一排
Knives out. Dead only. Dead only!
拔刀  只杀行尸  只杀行尸
Don't go anywhere.
哪也别去
Everyone, shots within 10 feet of the line.
所有人  10英尺以内再开枪
That's it.
就这样
Now!
开枪
No. We're not fighting them with you.
不  我们不会跟你们一起反抗他们
So take your damn guns and go.
拿着你们的枪滚吧
You win.
你赢了
No.
不
Get some people in here. Clean this up.
叫点人来  清理干净
What?
怎么了
You didn't actually think
你不会真的以为
I was gonna let you keep this, did you?
我会让你留着这把刀吧
You still got a ways to go
在我相信你效忠之前
before I'll believe you're fully on board here.
你还要走很长一段路
Baby steps.
一步步来嘛
It is absolutely not personal.
绝不是针对你
If the situation was reversed,
如果情况调过来
I'm sure you wouldn't believe me, either.
你肯定也不会相信我
Still...
但是
the way you saved yourself,
你自救的方式
the way you surrendered to me just now --
你刚向我投降的方式
That is a damn good start.
是个很好的开始
But we got to work on some things, Sasha.
但是  我们还得办点事  萨沙
But I promise you, I will try to make it fun.
不过我保证  我会尽量让过程充满乐趣
Cards on the table...
实话说了吧
a little birdie told me
一只小鸟告诉我
that Rick and the rest of your people are up to no good.
瑞克和你们其他的人在动歪脑筋
And, well, that needs to change,
这需要改变
and you're gonna help me change it.
而你要帮我改变
We're gonna find us a win-win.
我们会找到一个双赢的方法
How?
什么意思
- What are you - Hey, I'm gonna get you some stuff
-你打算...  -我会给你找些东西
to make you more comfortable,
让你更舒适
let you have a taste of what it is we have to offer.
让你体验一下我们能提供什么
Spend the night enjoying it,
好好享受一晚
'cause tomorrow...
因为明天
is gonna be a big day.
是个大日子
Kal!
凯尔
Yeah?
什么事
I'm gonna need you to drive me somewhere.
我需要你开车带我去个地方
You're gonna want to pack a bag.
你最好打个包
Hello?
在吗
It's Eugene.
我是尤金
Word in the halls is that you're all-in with things here.
听说你愿意加入这里了
It may not seem like it now,
现在也许看起来不像
but I assure you,
但我向你保证
you, too, made the correct select.
你同样做了正确的选择
I was wrong.
我错了
I can't.
我做不到
I won't.
我不会做
I've been sitting here,
我一直坐在这里
trying to figure out how I could,
想着我怎么能做到
with what happened,
发生了那么多事
with our friends still out there,
我们的朋友们还在外面
still being hurt by them.
还被他们伤害着
I don't know how I could've said that.
我不知道我怎么能那样说
And now...I am trapped.
现在  我陷入了困境
You have to help me.
你必须帮我
I will.
我会的
I'll help you get used to the idea
我会帮你习惯现实
and illustrate the equation and demonstrate why --
阐明利害  演示为什么...
It was a mistake.
那是个错误
I was ready.
我本来准备好了
I knew, if I didn't kill him last night,
我知道如果我昨晚没杀死他
it'd be over.
我就完了
And I didn't, so it is.
我没杀死他  所以就这样吧
It has to be.
必须这样
You have to get me something --
你必须给我搞些东西来
a knife, a gun, a razor blade.
刀  枪  剃须刀片
For Negan?
为了尼根吗
No!
不
One way or another, he is gonna use me to hurt my friends --
不管怎样  他都会利用我伤害我的朋友们
our friends.
我们的朋友们
And there is nothing I can do about it
而我对此无能为力
except make sure I'm not alive to give him the chance.
除非我死了  不给他机会
If he has me, he will hurt them.
只要我活着  他就会伤害他们
I have to die.
我必须死
It's the only way.
这是唯一的办法
I-I don't -- I-I don't think that --
我不认为...
I know you won't do anything to stop them.
我知道你不会做任何事阻止他们
I know that.
我知道
But, please, Eugene...
但是求你了  尤金
don't let them use me to hurt our people.
别让他们利用我伤害我们的人
Please, you have to give me something to stop this
求你了  你必须给我一些东西了断自己
-- a gun, a knife, glass.
枪  刀  玻璃
I don't care.
我不在乎
I have to die.
我必须死
Please.
求你了
I...
我...
I will consider it.
我会考虑
Thank you.
谢谢
We don't need all this, do we?
我们不需要全拿走吧
Yeah. Yeah, we do.
我们需要
It's not just the ones I killed.
不只是我杀的人
I think about the people I didn't kill, too.
我也会想起我没杀的人
We're gonna bring them back when it's all over.
结束后我们会把枪送回来
I-I want to go with you.
我想跟你们走
Some of us do, but not all of us,
我们有些人想反抗  但不是所有人
and it has to be all of us.
必须达成共识她们才加入
My grandmother thinks you'll all be dead.
我祖母认为你们都会死
Yeah, well, your grandmother's wrong about a lot of things.
你祖母很多想法都是错的
Where is she?
她人呢
She didn't want to see this.
她不想看见这个
She's lying down. I hit her pretty hard.
她躺下了  我把她打得挺重
Thanks for saving my life before.
感谢你之前救我命
And the other time.
还有另一次
?Maybe today.
也许还有今天
Thanks.
谢谢
For what you're doing.
你所做的事
You're not leaving us any?
不给我们留一把吗
Nope. See ya later, Rachel.
不留  回见  瑞秋
You okay?
你还好吧
Yeah.
还好
You're right.
你说得对
I don't have to feel bad.
我不必内疚
Sasha?
萨沙
I'm here.
我在
I've given our last exchange a good, hard pro/con think.
我仔细考虑权衡了上次谈话
I've decided to grant your request.
我决定满足你的请求
This will do it.
用这个就行
It's a poison, homemade by yours truly.
这是毒药  本人亲手制作
It will bring about certain death in approximately 20 to 30 minutes upon the moment of ingestion.
摄入后约20至30分钟内必死
I would like to believe that it's painless.
我相信应该是无痛的
I am not -- I'm not certain.
我不太确定
I made it at the behest of others for similar reasons,
我做药是因为曾有人提过类似请求
only it came to pass that they were feeding me the bum's steer,
后来我发现她们给了我虚假信息
so I cut bait.
于是我悬崖勒马
The difference here is that
现在的不同之处是
you and I have been long-time traveling companions,
我们俩是长期旅伴
and you have proven yourself to be honest, brave,
你证明了自己是一个诚实勇敢
and fully self-aware.
具备完全自我意识的人
I'm certain I owe you for things.
我确信我欠你人情
You asked me for a way out.
你让我帮你找解脱办法
I had access to one.
我找到了一个
For the record, I absolutely do not want you to go.
首先声明  我完全不希望你死
But it sounds to me like you happen to be already gone.
但是听起来你已经下了必死之心
Hey, are you okay?
你没事吧
Where's Sasha?
萨沙在哪
There's someone here.
有人来了
Slow down. Come on. Whoa!
慢点  等等
He says he wants to help us.
他说他想帮我们
That true?
是真的吗
You want to help?
你想帮忙
I do.
是的
Okay.
好
Get on your knees.
跪下